{
    "id": "cf2f891663bf4add8f6261ced0f96051",
    "title": "Ache, Pain, Hurt, Sore",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ............................... my knee while playing football yesterday.",
            "description": "To hurt your knee is to injure it.",
            "answers": [
                "pained",
                "ached",
                "hurt"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4d12d2a0e0d0498d8de11333854b60ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gargling with warm water will relieve the symptoms of a ............................... throat.",
            "description": "This is an example of a collocation. ",
            "answers": [
                "pain",
                "hurt",
                "sore"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "adaa48cfbff540dfa3e1984fe746adf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dentist can fix that ....................................",
            "description": "An ache is usually a mild discomfort that affects only a particular part of the body.\r\nPain is stronger.",
            "answers": [
                "ache",
                "hurt",
                "sore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92d315fa26984053a0f2ce7ca551814e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The blow made my head ......................................",
            "description": "An ache is usually a mild discomfort that affects only a particular part of the body.\r\nPain is stronger.",
            "answers": [
                "pain",
                "ache",
                "sore"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d868e2b49cfa4fa0a33de22156cf0ea5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The driver ....................................... himself badly in the accident.",
            "description": "Hurt is usually used as a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "pained",
                "ached",
                "sored"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "537553d72d8449148358da3f86d5665c"
        },
        {
            "question": "These new shoes .....................................",
            "description": "Hurt is usually a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "pain",
                "ache"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32839f0b232443cfb25cff8dd941fc1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy came home with a ...................................... knee.",
            "description": "A hurt knee is an injured knee.",
            "answers": [
                "paining",
                "ached",
                "hurt"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e18c0c01e1f4319b1b1025f83dc6746"
        },
        {
            "question": "The nurse bandaged my ..................................... toe.",
            "description": "Like hurt, sore can also be an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "paining",
                "hurting",
                "sore"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "37f947726a214ebea48f91af9c10abab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Losing the election was a .......................................... disappointment.",
            "description": "This is an example of a collocation. ",
            "answers": [
                "paining",
                "aching",
                "sore"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b05f9d9494a84bd1906af90b1cb57d75"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put some iodine on that .......................................",
            "description": "Sore can mean wound.",
            "answers": [
                "pain",
                "sore",
                "ache"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61a511bd52364e46bf4248af44791b82"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child's constant tantrums ......................................... his mother.",
            "description": "Pained can mean agonized or distressed.",
            "answers": [
                "ached",
                "pained",
                "sored"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6e0dbdcbf9446dc88e7ac6436cf9458"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a ..................................... in my shoulder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pain",
                "ache",
                "hurt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfe6fe98ff284702a8fbf4047e9b618e"
        }
    ]
}